

Jason Rostar

Web Developer, Programmer, & Designer

Web Developer with 5 years of experience creating attractive and responsive web apps with ReactJS, SASS, and with backend technologies such as NodeJS, Express, SQL. Experienced in deploying to services such as Heroku, Netlify, Vercel, GoDaddy and Github Pages. Worked remotely as database and systems administrator relying heavily on clear and concise communication with support from abroad.

\searrow	iason.rostar@vahoo.com
\sim	185011.1 USLAI (WVAI 100.COI 1

Southern Oregon

in linkedin.com/in/jasonrostarcmu

541-226-6367

jasonrostar.github.io/ExtendedResume/

github.com/JasonRostar

WORK EXPERIENCE

United States Navy ESS Team Lead

06/2016 - 05/2019

Responsibilities

- Electronic Security Systems Supervisor (ESS) In charge of a team consisting of five diverse military personnel who helped facilitate the successful installation of over \$8 million dollars in security equipment throughout NAVCONBRIG Miramar.
- Received Navy Marine Corps Achievement Medal for outstanding service during 3 year period working at the Miramar, California Brig.
- Actively pursued bachelors degree from Central Michigan University and Department of Labor Office Management certificate.

United States Navy

Aviation Maintenance Administration

02/2010 - 05/2016

Various Locations

Responsibilities

- Maintained server and database security and integrity, created and managed user account details, managed hardware and software upgrades contributing to the success of over 1000 mishap free MH-60B flight hours.
- Implemented and administered Local Area Networks (LAN) aboard U.S. Navy ships to support maintenance and flight operations contributing to the mission success of two West Pacific deployments.
- Managed an inventory of over 500 items; accurate accounting and upkeep resulted in the saving of over \$1M in maintenance costs for the Navy.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript HTML5

CSS3 SCSS

NodeJS Express

Test Driven Development ReactJS

React Hooks Redux

SQL TablePlus

Big O Notation Version Control

PERSONAL PROJECTS

jasonrostar.com (08/2019 - Present)

 Regularly updated to provide access to copies of bachelors degree, certificates, awards, etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) degree -Organizational and Business Administration

Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, Mi

08/2019

Degree Discription

 Formally educated in skills pertaining to the legal environment of business, communication, public relations, human resources, organizational psychology, and management through best practices.